autovillage.co.uk 2014-11-21

# AutoVillage Privacy Policy

#### 1\. This Privacy Policy

AutoVillage.co.uk is committed to protecting your personal information and other data provided to us via this and any other AutoVillage.co.uk web site ("Web Site"). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it contains important information about the use of information that you provide to us. This Privacy Policy explains what information AutoVillage.co.uk collects about you, and how we collect and use your information, including setting out the circumstances where we could provide it to third parties. You should also read the separate Site Visitor Agreement applicable to this Web Site.

#### 2\. What information do we collect and what do we do with it?

2.1 To take advantage of some of our services you will be required to log on or register with the Web Site. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. The information will be collected when you register with the Web Site in order to use any of the services available via the Web Site.

2.2 If you choose to advertise on the Web Site certain personal information or data (including credit card and billing information) about you will be captured electronically or otherwise. In the event that such personal information or data is part of your advert, such personal information or data will be posted to the Web Site may by viewed by users of the Web Site.

2.3 We may use the information that we collect to personalise your experience on the Web Site, to help you log on in future and to continue to use the Web Site, and to help us select services or materials for inclusion on the Web Site that may be of interest to you. We may need to pass your information to third parties who help us to maintain, administer or develop the Web Site but, if so, that information is only given to those third parties for that limited purpose.

2.4 We also monitor traffic patterns and usage of our Web Site to help us improve our Web Site design and layout. We may pass this information to our partners or other third parties but it will not contain any personally identifying information.

2.5 AutoVillage.co.uk may want to contact you to notify you of news about AutoVillage.co.uk, changes to the Web Site, special events or new services or products that we think may interest you. AutoVillage.co.uk may also use your details and information to communicate to you offers for services or goods from other websites owned by AutoVillage.co.uk group or other companies which we think may be of interest to you. However, AutoVillage.co.uk will not contact you for these purposes unless you authorise us to do so by either ticking the relevant boxes (i.e. during registration on the Web Site) to authorise AutoVillage.co.uk to make such contact, or you provide such authorisation in writing to AutoVillage.co.uk or electronically via the Web Site (if applicable). If, at any time thereafter, you change your mind and would rather not be contacted by AutoVillage.co.uk (or the third parties described above) to receive such information, please send an email to support@AutoVillage.co.uk with an explanation that you no longer wish to receive such information. In those circumstances, AutoVillage.co.uk will not contact you again in relation to the information described above in this paragraph 2.5. However, AutoVillage.co.uk and/or its group companies will still use your details to send you information and communications in relation to the services or products for which you have registered.

#### 3\. Sharing of Information with Third Parties

3.1 From time to time, AutoVillage may pass your details to carefully selected, trusted third parties so that they can also provide you with details of other services or products that might be of interest to you. If you do not wish us to do so, you should follow the procedure set out in paragraph 2.5 above and we will not provide your information to third parties for such purposes.

3.2 We follow security procedures as required by the UK Data Protection Act 1998, in the storage and disclosure of personal information that you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access to such information. At times we may let you know about the products or services provided by carefully selected third parties. We will only deal with partners who comply with the UK Data Protection Act 1998 as amended from time to time) and any other applicable data protection legislation or regulations, or with whom we are satisfied have appropriate measures to protect data. However, BuyYourLtd shall have no liability to you in respect of any breach of security by a third party.

#### 4\. Your Consent

4.1 You acknowledge and agree that:

4.1.1 in the course of using this Web Site or registering with it and any services offered via this Web Site, certain information about you will be captured electronically or otherwise and transmitted to AutoVillage or and, potentially, to any third parties as set out above or to third parties who host our web servers or assist us in maintaining this Web Site; and

4.1.2 AutoVillage may send your information outside of the European Economic Area for processing or use in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

4.2 You consent to the use, storage, or processing of your personal information by AutoVillage (or any third party AutoVillage uses for carrying out credit checks) for the purposes of carrying out any credit checks in the event that you enter into any financial transaction with AutoVillage.

4.3 If ordered by a court of competent jurisdiction to provide any of your personal information collected by AutoVillage as described in this Privacy Policy, you consent to AutoVillage providing such personal information to that court in accordance with the court's instructions.

4.4 By using this Web Site, you expressly agree to the collection and use of your information as set out above for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

#### 5\. Data Protection Indemnity

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, you acknowledge that in the course of you advertising goods or services on our Web Site, certain personal data about your employees, agents or subcontractors or certain personal data of third parties appearing in the advertising you requested to appear on our Web Site may be captured electronically or otherwise by us. If this is the case, you shall ensure that you have obtained the express consent of any employees, agents, subcontractors or any applicable third parties to the transfer of their personal data to us to use, store and process such personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, including where such personal data forms part of the advertising and is posted to the Web Site for accessed by users inside and outside of the European Economic Area. You shall indemnify AutoVillage from and against all claims by any employees, agents, subcontractors or any third parties arising out of your failure to obtain the consent described in this paragraph 5.

#### 6\. Our Responsibilities - How does AutoVillage protect Your Information?

6.1 When you enter into on-line credit or other payment card transactions (e.g. ordering advertising services on the Web Site), we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software encrypts the information that you input before it is transmitted to us. To prevent unauthorised access, we follow legally required security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information that you have given to us. This means that sometimes we may ask for proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.
